[
  {
    "question" : "The spell that Harry Potter used to bring his broom to him in the triwizard tournament was: True-Accio, False-Aparecium ",
    "answer" : true
  },
  {
    "question" : "The charm expelleriamus causes colorful sparks to fly out of the users wand",
    "answer" : false
  },
  {
    "question" : "The spell erecto erects items",
    "answer" : true
  },
  {
    "question" : "The spell Hermione corrects ron on in their first year was: True-Flipendo, False-Wingardium Leviosa",
    "answer" : false
  },
  {
    "question" : "The three unforgivable curses are Avada Kedavra,Imperio and Crucio ",
    "answer" : true
  },
  {
    "question" : "Petrificus Totalus does what: True- causes the victim to laugh historically, False- puts the victim in a full body bind ",
    "answer" : false
  },
  {
    "question" : "",
    "answer" : true
  },
  {
    "question" : "",
    "answer" : true
  },
  {
    "question" : "",
    "answer" : true
  },
  {
    "question" : "",
    "answer" : true
  }

]
